//13 question objects that app.js will reference correct and incorrect answers picked
var questionsLibrary = [
    {
        question: "Whats the capitol city of Oregon?",
        answers: ["Portland", "Salem", "Eugene", "Corvallis"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        image: "assets/images/"
    },
    {
        question: "What's Nephrology the study of?",
        answers: ["The Kidney", "The Immune System", "The Throat", "The Eyes"],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Whats the name of the Spy/Assassin Movie Trilogy starring Matt Damon?",
        answers: ["The Hobbit Trilogy", "The Bourne Trilogy", "Ocean's Thirteen", "Taken 3"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "What's the name of the Gorilla killed in the Cincinatti Zoo and turned into a meme?",
        answers: ["What a lame meme", "Hurrambe", "Harambe", "Mabootuu"],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "What computer language is being used to generate this quiz?",
        answers: ["C#", "C++", "Java", "Javascript"],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "In game of thrones, there has always been two rival families the show has followed throughout the show. Who are they?",
        answers: ["Starks/Grejoys", "Starks/Lannisters", "Starks/Boltons", "Lannisters/Tyrells"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Pick 1?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Pick 3?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Pick 3?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Pick 2?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Pick 4?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Pick 1?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        image: "assets/images"
    },
    {
        question: "Pick 1?",
        answers: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        image: "assets/images"
    }






];